Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, is waiting
where we should be going, go?
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride the waves.
We're all together as well, so
let's just stay with the sun.
While our dreams are never ending.
Heartbeat, we will be one, go ahead.
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see.
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Roger's treasure belongs to me
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow
we will find suspense And then commence
to live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our moths will never give up There's a
fire in our dreams And you can never,
never, never, never stop it
We will be one, go ahead!
Whoa!
You see what that shrimp did to him?
He just took down Spartan
like it was nothing!
That's insane!
He was one of the star
contenders of the Coliseum.
I don't know.
Maybe the Klutz just tripped over himself.
That wouldn't lodge you in the ground.
So? Where to?
Did you start a fight before the event?
I'm afraid that you're
going to have to leave.
What?
We don't need trash like you
causing brawls before the man's -
Come on!
Knock it off, you idiot!
The big guy started a
fight he couldn't handle.
He's the one you should disqualify
if he weren't unconscious.
They don't believe it—that's
Cyan Boo from Kano,
and that's not Chin Down behind them.
That guy's a living legend.
Thank you guys!
I owe you.
Hey, don't mention it, Pipsqueak!
pipsqueak
Yeah, that's right.
Don't mention it at all.
In fact, it kind of pisses me off when
I hear anyone say the words thank you.
Take it back!
Take back the credits,
you grateful bastard!
You don't have to reject
it that hard, bro.
If you ever say those words
to me again, I'll kill you!
Sorry.
Sometimes it gets a little worked up.
I guess that there's all
types out there. Dogama!
You ought to know it's pointless making
alliances with the other
big shots in your block!
Now that is a baseless
accusation, Kelly Funk.
Enough trash talk.
Lot of big names showing up.
You said it.
Looks like each country chose
to send their baddest dudes.
I was hoping for a fight
between gladiators,
but this is turning into a
war between nations over here.
First conspiracy and now bribery!
You make me sick, Dagama!
There's no point of lying with anyone.
Even if you cheat like that,
there's only one winner per block.
That means someone's gotta go down.
How about we cut the crap?
You're here on your
country's orders, same as me.
The flame flame fruit
gives you more than power.
It gives you prestige.
Most importantly, it gives you
a tactical military advantage.
Take a look around at
the faces in this room.
Let me tell you what I see.
Suleyman, the beheader.
Class A war criminal involved
in the Sea Battle of Diaz.
Abdullah and Jeet.
Former bounty hunters now wanted for their
savage attacks of government buildings.
Don't forget about our Lumbus, the
surmounter, the adventurer of lies.
Sponsored by the Don
Quixote family itself.
We have the sadistic hundred
million pirate, Bellamy the Hyena.
I also heard the pirate noble
Cavendish is gonna be here.
And the mad rookie Bartolomeo who
made waves in the new world last year.
Be honest.
You think with this room
of notorious characters?
no one is plotting to rig the match?
It'd be insane if we didn't have a plan.
I'm sure you two are up
to something as well.
Am I wrong?
The first challenge
here is a free-for-all.
Only one winner per block
goes to the next round. Yeah!
Block A's match is about to start.
Then B, C, and D will get their turns.
There's a grand total
of 550 competitors here.
As for the following round,
only four will move on!
The odds of winning are pretty slim,
but having your brother in the
same block should certainly help.
How fortunate!
Guess that's merely a coincidence and not
because you paid an
official to arrange it.
Just lucky, I guess.
Yup, just luck.
Which block do I find in?
The receptionist should
have told you already.
It says here that you're in block C.
I'm sure everyone here has got a
different reason to fight and depending
on whoever gets the flame flame fruit
The whole world could fall into chaos,
but that's the way it goes.
Good luck and may the best man win
armor helmets and swords
my head's about to
explode you mean we can
use whatever we want choose
anything except projectile weapons a half
-naked statue of an ancient
warrior dude Kick ass!
Can I have that?
Afraid not.
I'm gonna wear this armor and
helmet cooler than that old man's!
Ooh, and this too!
I wish Usopp and the
others could see me now!
Hey, what's wrong?
It's a nobleman.
A nobleman?
All the female staff are wilting
like daisies! What gives?
Just a peek is too much for me.
Well, I'll be damned.
That is Cavendish.
You mean the pirate noble?
I can't believe he's alive.
I can't believe he's so beautiful.
This is where we wait.
Degrading.
Ah, you over there.
Nice ensemble.
Alas, there is a weight
limit for gear, I'm afraid.
A limit?
Doesn't matter.
All the weapons and armor
in the world won't help you.
There's only one who deserves
the flame flame fruit.
Me.
Such beautiful power is wasted on you.
It's only fit for someone
equally as stunning.
You're over the weight limit.
I told you that earlier!
Get back here!
But I look so cool like this.
Is that why everyone's
running around half-naked?
Gladiators are nothing more
than a delivery system.
It's the blood of the loser.
That is what they thirst for.
This coliseum, it extracts the truth, strips
man down to his most authentic nature.
They don't want a protracted
match between sword and armor.
This competition's more
than just a show for them.
It's a release.
I don't have to take off the cape, right?
It looks so awesome on me.
Hey, Mew.
I saw you earlier.
Watched you crush that giant brute.
Made me wonder who you are. Me? Luffy.
What? No!
And I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
It says your name's Lucy!
Uh, yeah, Lucy.
Learn how to enunciate
better, you damn dolt!
So you're Lucy.
I almost crapped myself
thinking Straw Hat was here.
Oh, that little shrimp.
I heard the real Luffy's
over 20 feet tall.
His shield is awesome.
Lucky thing you're not him.
Because if you were the real Straw Hat
Luffy, I wouldn't wait for the ring.
I'd kill you now.
And why is that?
It's been three years since I
first arrived in the New World.
The entire globe was
entranced by the story of the
beautiful rookie with a 200
million bounty on his head.
I made the front page news every day.
Young women went nuts over my wanted
posters, and they became a collector's item.
They ripped them from
the walls of every town
so they could hang them in their bedrooms.
The world fell head over
heels in love with me,
and there's the shining
star who you mean me.
Well, who else but then?
A single freaking year later,
all anyone wanted to talk about
was the stupid war in Marine Ford.
Whitebeard stole the spotlight from me,
and Straw Hat Luffy stepped into it.
Right next to him, and on top of that,
a deluge of new rookies kept pouring in,
earning themselves the mantle of the worst
generation, and abducting the public's.
imagination.
The journalists practically forgot that
I even existed, and that's why I'm gonna
kill them.
These unworthy usurpers, they will die.
I think you got other
problems to work on, dude.
Say what you like.
To recapture the public adoration
I deserve, I will do anything it
takes and kill every rookie there is.
The first step is winning
today's prize, the flame flame
See?
Now you're qualified. Awesome!
No one will ever ignore me
again after I have won this!
You competing, dollface?
You ain't gonna last,
but you sure are cute.
What, you really don't know?
Aw, that's kinda funny.
I wound up wearing the same
fighting costume as this old guy.
Are you interested in him?
Huh?
Who are you?
I'm Rebecca, a gladiator here.
You made a fool of Spartan.
I hate that guy. Thanks for that.
This statue before you,
this man was a legend.
He was the greatest gladiator in the
whole history of the Corrida Coliseum.
Kiros.
He fought 3 ,000 matches and
claimed 3 ,000 victories.
The only wound he ever suffered
in combat was a single slash.
Wow, tough!
He was still fighting here
until just 20 years ago.
Even so, he is unknown to this country.
No one remembers a thing.
None of the elders, or
even the gladiators.
No one recalls having met him.
It's the most mysterious
statue in Dres Rosa.
He might not have existed for all we know.
Someone could have just made him up.
On top of that, who knows how
long this statue has been here?
All that we really know of the man is what
someone engraved on this placard here.
Even though we don't know who he is.
Nobody wants to remove the statue.
Another mystery.
Hmm, yeah, that's some pretty weird stuff.
But I gotta admit, it does look cool.
And super manly.
Yeah, I like it too.
Well, if it isn't Rebecca
the Great Warrior!
You think you can keep that
win record going out there?
I bet you're happy, huh?
About Spartan.
Your bully really got his
ass kicked, didn't he?
All right, knock it off,
you idiots. Let's go.
What's up with them?
Pay them no mind.
No more.
Today will be my final battle here.
I will take the Devil Fruit
prize for my own, and end this.
I will kill...
Doflamingo.
Mingo?
What block are you in?
C. That's good. I'm in D.
I'll cross my fingers for us.
I hope we both survive the first round.
Bye, Lucy.
Ah, we have a champion of blockade!
The masked man takes it all, Mr. Starr!
He ended the fight in a mere moment!
Hang on, it looks as though the mystery
man is about to remove his mask!
Is this happening?
The mask is off!
What?
I see!
It seems our mystery man is a fighter
famous across the whole world!
What a stunning opening
and an unexpected victor!
The winner of the Block
A Battle Royale is...
That guy?
The first division captain serving under
the fearsome warlord Emperor Blackbeard,
Jesus Burgess!
Whee!
That champion got us all the way back!
So the Blackbeard Pirates are in the mix.
I just expected Luffy to win
this tournament pretty easily,
but now, well, that might not be the case.
Here's hoping he doesn't
reveal himself somehow.
Well, I've got a job, so... Hey!
Not so fast! Please wait!
Quit it, you damn fool!
Enough already!
If you don't know where I can find the
factory, then you're worthless to me.
I gotta find a high-ranking
big shot in the Don
Quixote family and beat the location
out of it. So you... Be quiet.
Why should I?
We need to leave.
You can't voice such radical
views in a place like this.
All right, come clean.
Who the hell are you?
So, Hyruden, the pirate mercenary, and
Cavendish, and Gambia, the missionary?
Let's get out of here.
Hey, if you say so.
I don't get what the big rush is about.
Yeah, it's a pretty bad batch, alright.
It'll be big trouble if one of these
guys wins the flame flame fruit.
I'll talk to Esho right away.
You do that.
What's all this about?
What you doing, buddy?
Talking to yourself?
Now, hang on.
You ain't communicating with someone
on the outside, are you, pal?
Cause that would be fishy.
I'm right, aren't I?
And hey, what's that
you're writing down there?
I heard you whispering out the
names of the hottest pirates around.
Let me take a guess here.
You're not with the Navy.
Sir, are you still there?
Is everything all right?
Everything's fine.
Give me ten and I'll call you back.
Yes, sir.
Roger that.
The Coliseum is still thundering
from the excitement of blockade.
So I hope you bring the pain!
Time to make an exit.
I've heard enough.
Plenty of familiar
names to sound you long.
What's our next plan of action, sir?
Oh!
As a measure of safety, we should send
for no less than three Navy ships.
In the meanwhile, you and I, we'll
head for, uh, what was it called again?
Do you mean Greenbit? That's it.
We'll make our way there, and let's see.
We'll need, well, call for as
many medics as you possibly can.
There's a chance of civilian injuries.
Right. Yes, sir.
On the side of intel,
I want a head count of all
the people in the stands,
and the exact population of this town.
Wait, you want this instead
of the enemy numbers?
Is it that necessary?
The enemy, you said?
No.
That's not the number to worry about.
We should only be concerned with the
number of lives we need to protect first.
Yes, sir!
This is Mayna calling back.
Sorry for disconnecting earlier.
There's nothing to worry about here.
Oh, a name I mentioned, Gumby of the
Missionary, the one working for Bartolomeo.
Go ahead and cross his name off.
I had the wrong guy.
Damn it.
Navy, you bastard.
The plan is still on track, so
I'm going to keep moving forward.
So you're going to green bit huh?
You can, but I sure wouldn't recommend it.
Researchers, explorers—what
we're, uh, little of both,
whatever you want—is it
worth risking your life over?
Because it better be the bridge there—what
is it made of? It looks unusual.
it looks unusual
It's solid iron, but that
doesn't make it safe.
Well, that's obvious enough.
As you can see, nobody's
brave enough to use it.
There's a school of fighting fish nearby.
The seas around Green Bit
are full of the things.
Before those monsters moved in,
people used to go to and
from Green Bit all the time.
But that was about 200 years ago.
These fish, what are they like?
Nasty horns, nasty disposition.
take a ship and they'll
capsize you oh and they'll
attack the bridge too that's
what all those iron bars
are for although I hear
that barely slows them down
wait a sec they're fish
what do they fly out of the
water and tear straight
through solid iron maybe not
brave enough to see myself
I know plenty of people
who've tried to go but I
don't know anyone who's
come back what traffic what
gives why'd you pick such
a dangerous spot for
the trade-off no kidding
can't you hand me over
someplace nice you fool yeah no
point in complaining we're
already here more importantly
don't you think the
people in this country are
acting kind of strange the
flamingo said he stepped
down if they don't have a
king why is everybody so
calm we were taken by surprise
the moment we got here
that's what worries me hey
Robin is something wrong or
Uh...
Am I supposed to know those weirdos?
CP-0.
CP?
Wait a second.
The strongest intelligence
agents in the world.
Cypher-Pull, Aegis-0.
Like...
CP-9?
Please tell me they're not that tough.
I'm afraid that they're
much more dangerous.
You don't think they're here
because of my stone, do you?
Whatever their objective may be, if
they're here, it can't be good news.
I can't disagree.
I got you now, fairy!
I'll be taking my sword back, thank you!
Owie, ow, ow! Dang it!
I really messed up, and
human's gonna see me!
Run, you dummy!
Come on, hurry!
There's no need for hostility!
I'm just an old man passing by!
Not likely.
For starters, what's with
that topknot under your hat?
This?
No, it's simply a topknot-shaped hat!
Then take it off.
We saw you in the video Caesar
was broadcasting from Punk Hazard.
You samurai are big on honor, aren't you?
You had to come back.
And we were ready for you.
Evidently not ready enough!
Whoa, easy there.
If you don't want your buddy Conjuro
to get hurt, you put that away.
The target is in sight.
We're safe now!
Dearest Nami, dearest Robin, I hope
the weather is nice where you are.
Yee-hoo!
My goodness.
You're strong.
That was amazing. No, no.
Anyone can detect a sniper
from over a hundred feet away.
It was nothing at all, really.
Oh, my hero.
As for me, I'm trapped in a hurricane.
That is to say, a hurricane called love.
You can always count on me.
Wrong! All wrong!
You're not supposed to
drink the tea, you fool!
You test for poison!
Then, once you're certain that it's safe,
you give the tea to the Shogun, who is me!
If it's not safe, then you
simply die! Get it? Uh-huh!
Do it again, Choppa Amon!
My tea!
As you wish!
I shall return shortly with your beverage!
Shogun, I hope that my
lap is to your liking.
It is most satisfactory.
In fact, I might stay
like this all day long.
I see.
You're welcome to do so, my lord.
I might stay like this all day.
How awful of you!
And why?
Oh, you mean this wasn't a
sleeping-on-your-lap party?
What'd you think, Brooke? Play along. Hmm?
It's a game, pretending
Momo's the showgun.
I'm afraid I don't follow.
It's sad.
If we leave Momo alone, he gets all depressed
about something and nobody knows why.
He doesn't want to share it with us, but I
think he went through something real bad.
Huh?
I didn't notice myself,
but I trust your opinion.
Hey, Bonekichi! Yes?
You're a funny fellow.
Try to amuse me.
Sorry.
See, I only take orders
from Captain Luffy.
Don't you know, whoa, don't you know.
You can't keep a good corpse down.
Bury me deep, you won't hear a peep.
But soon enough I'll
wake up from my sleep.
Yeah!
Mentality!
It ain't got nothin' on me! Yeah!
Thank you, everybody!
I don't like it. Uh-oh. What's that?
We're the only people on
this sunny, aren't we?
I thought so.
Is it a ghost? Creepy!
I'm scared!
Help!
Dorry me, this won't do.
Oh, it's coming from the men's dormitory.
This won't do at all.
I saw it brought them back from the desk!
Is it the enemy?
Competitors of Block B,
report to the arena now!
Has anyone seen Capman?
Bartolomeo, it's time to go!
Ah, there you are.
Bartolomeo, right?
Hey, Block B is starting.
Got it.
Have you seen a competitor called Capman?
He's still missing.
Nah, sorry, pal.